Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/bryan-kiew-370988164 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Business Development

Mandarin

Executive Operations Management

Bryan Kiew

CEO at SHUANGFEI WIRE HARNESS MALAYSIA Selangor

Summary

Experienced Business Development Operations Manager with a demonstrated history of working in the electrical and electronic manufacturing industry. Skilled in Market Planning, International Sales, Cantonese, Mandarin, and Business Development. Strong business development professional graduated from Tunku Abdul Rahman University College.

Experience

SHUANGFEI WIRE HARNESS MALAYSIA CEO

December 2019 - Present (2 years 1 month)

Selangor, Malaysia

IASB Malaysia

Manager (Business development & Operation)
October 2009 - December 2019 (10 years 3 months)

Selangor, Malaysia

Responsible to manage the revenue, P&L and business development of the company.

Success to evolve the company from just a trading based company to a first tier sub-contracting business company & manage to growth revenue up to 3 fold.

Continue to bring in new idea & new business modal for the organic and in organic growth of the company.

French MNC
Business Unit Manager
August 1997 - July 2009 (12 years)
Selangor, Malaysia

Responsible to take up the business unit on Electronics componenets distribution in Malaysia & Singapore. Direct report to MD & resposible for business growth, new product/business development, P&L and operation of the business unit.

Manage to build the business from scratch to about USD15mil with double digit net profit.

Recognized as the top most efficient business units in the company (lowest working capital, highest net profit and highest revenue growth within 5 years). Total work force in the business unit: 5

Education

Tunku Abdul Rahman University College Pre U · (1990 - 1992)